
[
    {
      "question": "The acronym PC stands for?",
      "choice1": "<Private Computer>",
      "choice2": "<Personal Computer>",
      "choice3": "<Personal Compact>",
      "choice4": "<Personal Compass>",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is software?",
      "choice1": "<Any part of the computer that has a physical structure>",
      "choice2": "<Flexible parts of a computer case>",
      "choice3": "<Clothing designed to be worn by computer users>",
      "choice4": "<Instructions to tell the hardware what to do>",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The computers main circuit board is called a ...?",
      "choice1": "<Hard drive>",
      "choice2": "<Motherboard>",
      "choice3": "<Monitor>",
      "choice4": "<Bluetooth card>",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
     "question": "RAM is like a computer’s ________, while a hard drive is like a computer’s ________.?>",
      "choice1": "<Long-term memory/short-term memory>",
      "choice2": "<Nervous system/brain>",
      "choice3": "<Short-term memory/long-term memory>",
      "choice4": "<Brain/nervous system>",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "What is an Ethernet port used for>?",
      "choice1": "<Creating new user accounts",
      "choice2": "<Connecting smartphones and other peripherals>",
      "choice3": "<Connecting to the Internet",
      "choice4": "<Providing power to the computer",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "What is Wi-Fi?",
        "choice1": "<A type of wireless network>",
        "choice2": "<An extra-wide computer case used by servers>",
        "choice3": "<A type of software that scans for viruses>",
        "choice4": "<A type of sound card>",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Windows, macOS, and Linux are examples of ________.?",
        "choice1": "<Mobile Devices>",
        "choice2": "<Internet service providers>",
        "choice3": "<Operating systems>",
        "choice4": "<Web Browsers>",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "What does GUI stand for?",
        "choice1": "<Gateway using Intel>",
        "choice2": "<Good used iPhone>",
        "choice3": "<Global user index>",
        "choice4": "<Graphical user interface>",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does GUI stand for?",
            "choice1": "<Gateway using Intel>",
            "choice2": "<Good used iPhone>",
            "choice3": "<Global user index>",
            "choice4": "<Graphical user interface>",
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "The malicious software program, which is detrimental to other computer programs is known as …?",
                "choice1": "<Virus>",
                "choice2": "<Trojans>",
                "choice3": "<Worns>",
                "choice4": "<Spyware>",
                "answer":  1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you need to copy the contents of MS Word, which command will you give?",
                "choice1": "<Ctrl+X>",
                "choice2": "<Ctrl+C>",
                "choice3": "<Ctrl+V>",
                "choice4": "<Ctrl+Z>",
                "answer":  2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which among the following correctly defines the term data processing?",
                "choice1": "<Data input in computer>",
                "choice2": "<Data output from computer>",
                "choice3": "<A&B>",
                "choice4": "<To retrieve, transform, or classify information in a computer>",
                "answer":  4
        },
        {
            "question": "USB is a ... storage device?",
                "choice1": "<Primary>",
                "choice2": "<Secondary>",
                "choice3": "<Auxiliary>",
                "choice4": "<Additional>",
                "answer":  2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which among the following correctly defines the term backup?",
                "choice1": "<Linking one computer system with multiple computers>",
                "choice2": "<Classifying data in different groups>",
                "choice3": "<Separating a computer system from the group of computers>",
                "choice4": "<Copying and saving data from the original source to other secure destination>",
                "answer":  4
        },
        {
            "question": "What is hardware?",
                "choice1": "<Linking one computer system with multiple computers>",
                "choice2": "<Classifying data in different groups>",
                "choice3": "<Separating a computer system from the group of computers>",
                "choice4": "<Copying and saving data from the original source to other secure destination>",
                "answer":  4
        },
        {
            "question": "... computer is the most powerful computer.?",
                "choice1": "<Mini>",
                "choice2": "<Micro>",
                "choice3": "<Super>",
                "choice4": "<Mainframe>",
                "answer":  3
        },
        {
            "question": " What is processed by the computer into information.?",
                "choice1": "<Data>",
                "choice2": "<Processor>",
                "choice3": "<Numbers>",
                "choice4": "<Input>",
                "answer":  1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is called the starting up on operating system??",
                "choice1": "<Starting>",
                "choice2": "<Entering>",
                "choice3": "<Booting>",
                "choice4": "<Formatting>",
                "answer":  3
        },
        {
            "question": "The first computer was programmed using?",
                "choice1": "<Assembly language>",
                "choice2": "<Machine language>",
                "choice3": "<Source code>",
                "choice4": "<Object code>",
                "answer":  2
        },
        {
            "question": "...IC stands for?",
                "choice1": "<Internal Circuit>",
                "choice2": "<Internal Computer>",
                "choice3": "<Integrated Computer>",
                "choice4": "<Integrated Circuit>",
                "answer":  4
        }
  ]
